Finding Aid for the Delbert Mann Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Delbert Mann Papers
multiple
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0646
42.42 linear_feet
- Photographs
  - All Quiet on the Western Front -1979
    - 1-10 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 11-20 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 21-30 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 31-40 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 41-50 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 51-60 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 61-70 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 71-80 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 81-90 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 91-100 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 101-110 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 111-120 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 121-130 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 131-140 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 141-150 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 151-160 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 161-170 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - All Quiet on the Western Front-1979
    - 171-180 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - 181-190 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - 191-200 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - 201-210 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - 211-220 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - 221-230 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - 231-240 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - 241-250 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - 251-260 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - 261-270 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - 271-280 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - 281-290 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - 291-300 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - 301-310 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - 311-320 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - 321-330 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - 331-340 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - 341-350 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - All Quiet on the Western Front-1979, 351-360 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - 361-370 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 371-373 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - All the Way Home -1981, 1-5 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - April Morning-1987, 1-10 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - 11-20 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - 21-30 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - 31-40 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - 41-50 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - 51-60 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - 61-70 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - 71-77 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Bachelor Party-1956, 1-10 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - 11-20 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - 21-30 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - 31-40 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - 41-47 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Birch lnterval-1974, 1-10 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - 11-12 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Breaking Up-1976, 1-10 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - 11-20 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - 21-25 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Bronte-1982, 1-10 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - 11-20 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - 21-30 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - 31-40 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - 41-50 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - 51-60 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Dark at the Top of the Stairs-1960, 1-10 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - 11-20 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - 21-30 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - 31-40 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - 41-48 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - David Copperfield, 1969, 1-10 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - 11-20 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - 21-30 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - 31-40 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - 41-46 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - The Day Lincoln Was Shot-1956, 1-10 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - 11-20 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - 21-30 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Dear Heart-1963, 1-10 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - 11-20 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - 21-30 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - 31-40 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Dear Heart-1963, 41-50 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - 51-60 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - 61-70 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - 71-80 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - 81-83 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - A Death in California-1985, 1-10 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - 11-20 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - 21-30 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - 31-40 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - 41-50 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - 51-60 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Desire Under the Elms-1957, 1-10 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - 11-20 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - 21-30 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - 31-40 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - 41-50 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - 51-52 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - First Woman President-1974, 1-10 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - 11-20 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - 21- (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Fitzwilly-1966, 1-10 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - 11-20 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - 21-30 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - 31-40 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - 41-45 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Francis Gary Powers Story-The U2 Spy Plane, 1-6 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - A Gathering of Eagles-1962, 1-10 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - 11-20 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - 21-30 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - 31-40 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - 41-50 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - 51-60 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - 61-70 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - 71-80 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - 81-90 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - 91-100 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - 101-110 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - 111-120 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - 121-130 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - 131-140 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - 141-150 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - 151-153 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - The Gift of Love: A Christmas Story-1983, 1-10 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - 11-20 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - 21-30 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - 31-40 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - A Girl Named Sooner-1974, 1-10 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - 11-20 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - 21-30 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - 31-40 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - 41-50 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - 51-60 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - God’s Guerillas-1981, 1- (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Heidi-1967, 1-10 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - 11-20 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - 21-30 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - 31-40 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - 41-42 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Home to Stay-1977, 1-10 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - 11-20 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - 21-26 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Incident in a Small Town-1993, 1-10 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - 11-20 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - 21-30 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - 31-40 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - 41-50 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - 51-54 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Incident in Baltimore-1991, 1-10 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - 11-20 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - 21-30 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - 31-40 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - 41-50 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - lronclads-1991, 1-10 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - 11-20 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - 21-30 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - 31-40 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - 41-50 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - 51-56 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Jane Eyre-1970, 1-10 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - 11-21 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - 21-30 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - 31-40 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Jane Eyre-1970, 41-50 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 51-60 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - 61-70 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - 71-80 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Kidnapped-1971, 1-10 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - 11-20 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - 21-30 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - 31-40 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - 41-50 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - 51-60 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - 61-70 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - 71-80 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - 81-90 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - 91-100 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - 101- (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Last Days of Patton-1985, 1-10 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - 11-20 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - 21-30 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - 31-40 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - 41-50 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - 51-53 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Legendary Curse of the Hope Diamond-1975, 1-10 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - 11-20 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - 21-30 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - 31- (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Lily in Winter-1994, 1-10 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - 11-20 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Love Leads the Way-1984, 1-10 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - 11-20 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - 21-30 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - 31-40 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - 41-50 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - 51-60 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - 61-70 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - 71-80 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - 81-90 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - 91-100 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - 101-110 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - 111-120 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - 121-125 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Lover Come Back, 1961, 1-10 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - 11-20 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - 21-30 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - 31-40 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - 41-50 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - 51-60 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - 61-70 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - 71-80 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - 81-89 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Love’s Dark Ride-1978, 1-2 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - The Man Without a Country-1973, 1-10 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - 11-16 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Marty-1954, 1-10 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - 11-20 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - 21-30 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - 31-40 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - 41-50 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - 51-60 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - 61-70 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - 71-80 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Member ofthe Wedding-1982, 1-10 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - 11-15 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - The Memoirs of Abraham Lincoln-1990, 1992, 1-10 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - 11-20 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - 21-24 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Middle of the Night-1959, 1-10 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - 11-20 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - 21-30 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - 31-40 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - 41-50 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - 51-60 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - 61-70 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Middle of the Night-1959, 71-80 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - 81-90 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - 91-100 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - 101-110 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - 111-120 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - 121-130 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - 131-140 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - 141-150 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - 151-160 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - 161- (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Mister Buddwing-1964, 1-10 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - 11-20 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - 21-30 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - 31-40 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - 41-50 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - 51-60 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Mister Buddwing-1964, 61-70 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - 71-80 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - 81-90 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - 91-100 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - 101-110 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - 111-120 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - 121-130 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - 131-140 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - 141-150 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - 151-160 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - 161- (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Night Crossing-1980, 1-10 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - 11-20 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - 21-30 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - 31-40 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - 41-50 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - 51-60 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - 61-70 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - 71-80 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - 81-90 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - 91-100 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - 101-110 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - 111-120 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - 121-130 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - 131-140 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - 141-1501 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - 151-160 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Night Crossing-1980, 161-170 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - 171-180 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - 181-190 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - 191-200 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - 201-210 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - 211-220 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - 221-230 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - 231-240 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - 241-250 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - 251-260 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - 261-270 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - 271-280 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - 281-290 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - 291-300 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - 301-310 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - 311-320 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - 321-330 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - 331-340 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - 341-350 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - 351-360 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - 361-370 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - 371-380 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Night Crossing-1980, 381-390 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - 391-400 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - 401-410 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - 411-420 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - 421-430 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - 431-440 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - 441-450 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - 451-460 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - The Outsider-1960, 1-10 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - 11-20 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - 21-30 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - 31-40 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - 41-50 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - 51-60 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - 61-70 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - 71-80 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - 81-90 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - 91-99 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - The Pink Jungle-1967, 1-10 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - 11-17 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Plot to Kill Stalin-1958, 1-10 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - 11-20 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - 21-27 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - A Quiet Place-1955, 1-7 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Quick, Before it Melts-1963, 1-10 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - 11-20 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - 21-30 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - 31-40 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - 41-50 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - 51-60 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - 61-70 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - 71-72 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Separate Tables-1958, 1-10 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - 11-20 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - 21-30 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - 31-40 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - 41-50 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - 51-60 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - 61-70 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - 71-80 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - 81-90 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - 91-100 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - 101-110 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - 111-120 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - She Waits- 1972, 1- (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Speaking of Murder-1956, 1-10 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - 11-12 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - The Ted Kennedy Jr. Story-1986, 1-10 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - 11-20 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - 21-30 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - 31-40 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - 41-50 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - 51-60 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - 61-70 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - 71- (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Thou Shall Not Commit Adultery-1978, 1-10 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - 11-20 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - 21-30 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - To Find My Son-1980, 1-10 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - 11-20 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - 21-30 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - 31-35 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Tom and Joann-1978, 1-10 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - 11-19 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Torn Between Two Loves-1979, 1-10 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - 11-14 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Touch of Mink-1962, 1-10 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - 11-20 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - 21-30 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - 31-40 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Touch of Mink-1962, 41-50 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - 51-60 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - 61-70 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - 71-80 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - 81-90 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - 91-100 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - 101-110 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - 111-120 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - 121-130 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - 131-140 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - 141-149 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Tovarich-1962, 1-9 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Three for a Wedding-1964, 1-4 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - The Tunnel-1959, 1-10 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - 11-20 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - 21-30 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - 31-40 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - What Makes Sammy Run?-1959, 1-3 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Producer’s Showcase-1955-Darkness at Noon, 1-10 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - 11-12 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Producer’s Showcase-1955-Marty, 1- (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Producer’s Showcase-1955-Our Town, 1-10 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - 11-17 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Producer’s Showcase-1955-The Petrified Forest, 1-10 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - 11-20 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Producer’s Showcase-1955-Yellow Jack, 1-2 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Town Theatre –Columbia, S.C. –The Barretts of Wimpole Street, 1-10 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Town Theatre –Columbia, S.C. –Command Decision, 1-5 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Town Theatre –Columbia, S.C. –The Corn is Green, 1-10 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - 11-18 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Town Theatre –Columbia, S.C. –Dear Ruth, 1-10 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - 11- (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Town Theatre –Columbia, S.C. –Dream Girl, 1-10 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - 11-20 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - 21-23 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Town Theatre –Columbia, S.C. –The Glass Menagerie, 1-5 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Town Theatre –Columbia, S.C. –Highland Fling, 1-6 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Town Theatre –Columbia, S.C. –John Loves Mary, 1-10 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Town Theatre –Columbia, S.C. –Life With Father, 1-6 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Town Theatre –Columbia, S.C. –Rain, 1-5 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Town Theatre –Columbia, S.C. –The Road to Rome, 1-3 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Town Theatre –Columbia, S.C. –You Can’t take it with You, 1-3 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Town Theatre –Columbia, S.C. -1988, 1-10 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - 11-20 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - 21-24 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Town Theatre –Columbia, S.C. -1992-1993, 1-10 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - 11-15 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - TV Playhouse 1949-1950, 1-9 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - TV Playhouse 1949, 1-4 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - TV Playhouse 1950 –Bonanza, 1-10 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - TV Playhouse 1950 –The Feast, 1-5 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - TV Playhouse 1950 –The Last Tycoon, 1-9 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - TV Playhouse 1950 –The Sudden Guest, 1-6 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - TV Playhouse 1950 –othello, 1-10 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - 11-16 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - TV Playhouse 1950 –Vincent van Gogh, 1-10 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - 11-13 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - TV Playhouse 1951, 1-3 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - TV Playhouse 1951 –The Adventures of Hiram Holiday, 1-2 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - TV Playhouse 1951 –The Birth ofthe Movies, 1-9 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - TV Playhouse 1951 –Bulletin 120, 1-10 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - 11-20 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - 21-30 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - 31-34 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - TV Playhouse 1951 –By-line for Murder, 1-3 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - TV Playhouse 1951 –The Copper, 1-3 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - TV Playhouse 1951 –The Eleventh Ward, 1- (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - TV Playhouse 1951 –Fiight to Freedom, 1-2 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - TV Playhouse 1951 –I Was Stalin’s Prisoner, 1-6 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - TV Playhouse 1951 –Justice for Mr. Pleznick, 1-3 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - TV Playhouse 1951 –Money to Burn, 1- (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - TV Playhouse 1951 –October Story, 1- (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - TV Playhouse 1951 –Operation Airlift, 1-5 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - TV Playhouse 1951 –Pretend I am a Stranger, 1-2 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - TV Playhouse 1951 –The Return, 1-2 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - TV Playhouse 1951 –A Secret Island, 1-4 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - TV Playhouse 1951 –This Time Next Year, 1-5 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - TV Playhouse 1952 –The Best Laid Schemes, 1-3 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - TV Playhouse 1952 –Dusty Portrait, 1-10 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - 11-13 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - TV Playhouse 1952 –The Five Fathers of Pepi, 1-3 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - TV Playhouse 1952 –The Lantern Copy, 1- (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - TV Playhouse 1952 –The Last Hour, 1- (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - TV Playhouse 1952 –The Medea Cup, 1- (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - TV Playhouse 1952 –The Monument, 1-2 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - TV Playhouse 1952 –Mr. Quimby’s Christmas Hats, 1- (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - TV Playhouse 1952 –Parole Chief, 1- (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - TV Playhouse 1952 –The Rich Boy, 1-9 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - TV Playhouse 1952 –Search, 1-9 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - TV Playhouse 1952 –Segment, 1-3 (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - TV Playhouse 1952 –Three Sundays, 1-2 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - TV Playhouse 1952 –Without Fear or Favor, 1-3 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - TV Playhouse 1953, 1-5 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - TV Playhouse 1953 –The Bachelor Party, 1- (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - TV Playhouse 1953 –Catch a Falling Star, 1-2 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - TV Playhouse 1953 –Double Jeopardy, 1- (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - TV Playhouse 1953 –Elegy, 1-3 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - TV Playhouse 1953 –Ernie Barger is 50, 1- (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - TV Playhouse 1953 –Her Prince Charming, 1- (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - TV Playhouse 1953 –Holiday Song, 1-2 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - TV Playhouse 1953 –Hollywood Tandem, 1-2 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - TV Playhouse 1953 –A Little Something in Reserve, 1- (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - TV Playhouse 1953 –Marty, 1-10 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - TV Playhouse 1953 –Othello, 1-4 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - TV Playhouse 1953 –Printer’s Measure, 1- (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - TV Playhouse 1953 –Reluctant Citizen, 1- (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - TV Playhouse 1953 –Wings on My Feet, 1- (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - TV Playhouse 1953 –Wish on the Moon, 1- (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - TV Playhouse 1954 –And Crown Thy Good, 1- (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - TV Playhouse 1954 –Hangman in the Fog, 1- (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - TV Playhouse 1954 –The Mother, 1-10 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - TV Playhouse 1954 –Somebody Special, 1- (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - 55th Vanderbilt Reunion, 1-10 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - 11-16 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Aldrich Award, DGA, 1997, 1-8 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Nashville Playhouse, 1-4 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Nashville Playhouse –Emperor’s New Clothes, 1-2 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Nashville Playhouse 1942 –Mr. and Mrs. North, 1-5 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Nashville Playhouse 1940 –Our Town, 1-10 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - 11-12 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Nashville Playhouse 1941 –Qutward Bound, 1-2 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Nashville Playhouse -Sailors of Toulon, 1-5 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Nashville Playhouse 1940 –Twelfth Night, 1-2 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Nashville Community Playhouse 1961, 1-3 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Academy Award Tribute, March 1, 1988, 1-10 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Hume-Fogg High School, 1-3 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Vanderbilt University, 1-10 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - 11-16 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Wellesley Summer Theatre 1947-1948, 1-10 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - 11-20 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - 21-24 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Yale University 1945-1947, 1-10 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - 11-20 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - 21-30 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - 31-40 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - 41-50 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - 51-60 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - 61- (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Yale Drama School 1991, 1-2 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Photographs Folders
  - Tim and Joann, 1978 (Box 2)
  - Francis Gary Powers Story the U-2 Spy Plane (Box 2)
  - Breaking Up 197? (Box 2)
  - The Legendary Curse of the Hope Diamond, 1975 (Box 2)
  - Thou Shalt Not Commit Adultery, 1978 (Box 2)
  - Torn Between Two Loves, 1979 (Box 2)
  - All Quiet On the Western Front–Publicity Materials (Box 2)
  - All Quiet On the Western Front–Photographs and Slides (Box 2)
  - All Quiet On the Western Front (Box 2)
  - TV Playhouse, 1949-1950 (Box 2)
  - Town Theatre Pictures Columbia, S.C., 1947-1949 (Box 2)
  - The Outsider, 1960 (Box 2)
  - Lover Come Back, 1961 (Box 2)
  - Touch of Mink, 1962 (Box 2)
  - Nashville Playhouse (Box 2)
  - Vanderbilt, 1939-41 (Box 2)
  - Hume Fogg High, 1937 (Box 3)
  - Love’s Dark Ride, 1978 (Box 3)
  - Home to Stay, 1977 (Box 3)
  - Tell Me My Name, 1977 (Box 3)
  - The First Woman President, 1974 (Box 3)
  - The Glass Menagerie (Atlanta) (Box 3)
  - A Girl Named Sooner, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Birch Interval, 1974 (Box 3)
  - The Man Without a Country, 1973 (Box 3)
  - She Waits, 1972 (Box 3)
  - Kidnapped, 1971 (Box 3)
  - Jane Eyre, 1970 (Box 3)
  - David Copperfield, 1969 (Box 3)
  - Heidi, 1967 (Box 3)
  - The Pink Jungle, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Fitzwilly, 1966 (Box 3)
  - Mister Buddwing, 1964 (Box 3)
  - 3 For a Wedding, 1964 (Box 3)
  - Quick, Before it Melts, 1963 (Box 3)
  - Dear Heart, 1963 (Box 3)
  - Tovarich, 1962 (Box 3)
  - A Gathering of Eagles, 1962 (Box 3)
  - Lily in Winter, 1994 (Box 3)
  - Incident in a Small Town, 1993 (Box 3)
  - The Memoirs of Abraham Lincoln, 1990 and 1992 (Box 3)
  - The Petrified Forest, 1988 (Box 3)
- December 2008
  - Videocassettes
    - THE BACHELOR PARTY (Box 1)
    - BEN FRANKLIN, 1972 (Box 1)
    - BIRCH INTERVAL, THE MAKING OF. .. ROBERT TAYLOR’S BACKYARD, DEL AT WORK, GETTYSBURG, PA, 1977 (Box 1)
    - BREAKING UP, 1976 (Box 1)
    - DARK AT THE TOP OF THE STAIRS, 1960 (Box 1)
    - FITZWILLY –PRO; INSPECTOR CLOUSEAU – PRO; PARTY- PRO – DEMO TAPE FOR LARRY MIRISCH (Box 1)
    - FRANCIS GARY POWERS: THE TRUE STORY OF THE U-2 INCIDENT (Box 1)
    - GOLDEN VOICES, S/LVER SCREEN (Box 1)
    - GREAT CATHERINE – NBC THEATRE GUILD (Box 1)
    - HOLIDAY SONG – PHILCO TELEVISION PLAYHOUSE, 1953 (Box 1)
    - INPRINT - SKUTCH/MANN BEVERLY HILLS PUBLIC TELEVISION (Box 1)
    - THE INWARD HORIZON (Box 1)
    - LOVE LEADS THE WAY, 1984 (Box 1)
    - MAKING IT SPECIAL (Box 1)
    - THE MARRIAGES, 1950 (Box 1)
    - MARTY (Box 1)
    - MARTY, 1993 (Box 1)
    - MARTY (Box 1)
    - A WIND FROM THE SOUTH (Box 1)
    - MARTY – INTERVIEW WITH DELBERT MANN (Box 1)
    - MARY KAY AND JOHNNY SHOW, 1949 (Box 1)
    - MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT (Box 1)
    - MR. QUIMBY’S CHRISTMAS HATS- GOODYEAR TELEVISION PLAYHOUSE, 1952 (Box 1)
    - THE MOTHER – PHILCO TELEVISION PLAYHOUSE (Box 1)
    - NIGHT CROSSING (Box 1)
    - OMNIBUS: THE HARVARD SHOW (Box 1)